jansgalleries.com 2004-06-02

# Jans! Webring - User Agreement

**This Privacy Policy applies to the following websites: (1) www.janswebring.com (collectively, the “Sites”, or individually, a “Site”).**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Sites. By accessing and using our Sites, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Sites. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. 

**Information Collection and Use  
**We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Sites. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points throughout our Sites.

**Registration Form**  
To become a member of our Sites, a user must complete the on-line registration form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include your full name, mailing address, and e-mail address). This information is used to set-up and maintain an account, verify credit card details, validate credit identity. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.   

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Sites. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Sites, we are able track IP addresses and browser preferences in order to enhance and personalize your experience at our Sites. We may also use cookies in order to track referral sites in order to properly compensate our affiliates.

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use an outside company or companies to process payments or to fulfill orders. From time to time, we may contract with another party to provide certain specific services to our users. If we have collected your personally identifiable information from one Site, that Site may share the information with other Sites within our network in order to provide you with additional goods and services for which we believe you may be interested.

**Law Enforcement**  
We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child pornography. 

**Links**  
The Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our Sites they should read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

**Security**  
We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures. 

**Third Party Sources of Information**  
From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive from you with information we obtain from third party sources. 

**Children**  
Our Sites are not intended for children. Our Sites do not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. 

**Correction/Updating Personal Information**  
If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as phone number or a credit card number), or if a user no longer desires our service, you may contact us to correct or update this information. 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
From time to time, we may send our users e-mail or other notices regarding new services, promotions, or other information which may be of general interest. Users who no longer wish to receive materials from us may opt-out of receiving these communications by contacting us. 

**Notification of Changes**  
We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Sites. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use any of our Sites, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use any of our Sites after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or if you otherwise need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please contact us by sending an e-mail. Please provide us with your password, username and account number so we can service you quicker.   
For www.janswebring.com and its related sites, please send your e-mail to: [support@janswebring.com](mailto:support@janswebring.com).
